Phrasal verbs. When you have a verb and a preposition, it's called a phrasal verb.
These are idiomatic expressions that can't be translated literally. They tend to be
stressed on the second word, such as sit down, fall off, get up, put away, come
back, et cetera. If you have a phrasal verb, such as pick up, and you put the
stress on the first word, it turns into a noun meaning truck, as in he was driving a
pickup truck. Don't come back. He's planning his big comeback. Let's back up
and start again. Do you have a backup plan? The children have run off. The sewer
runoff polluted the stream. Could you print this out? Could you make a printout?
They broke up last week. It was a terrible breakup. Could you call me back? I'm still
waiting for a callback. We're going to have to cut back. The cutbacks are ruining
the program. Sure, go ahead. We got the go-ahead. We need to work around the
problem. He came up with a good workaround. The heirlooms were handed
down. I won't wear hand-me-downs. How much was left over? What? Leftovers again? It
didn't work out. It was a great workout. The dogs ran away. It was a runaway
bestseller. He knocked me down and dragged me out. It was a knock-down, drag-out
fight.